(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Crazyになるほど恋しているZOMBIE
I'm a Zombie in Love to the Point of Going Crazy
HOLOLIVE INDONESIA SECOND GENERATION
KUREIJI OLLIE PRESENT
Crazyになるほど恋しているZOMBIE
I'm a Zombie in Love to the Point of Going Crazy
your startled face is so cute~
キミのびっくりした顔、ほんっとにかわいいよね〜
Wasn't this what you were waiting for?
これって、ずっと楽しみにしてたんじゃないの〜？
To be able to talk to your oshi~
だって、推しと直接お話できるんだよ〜？
Hmm, why the frantic button pressing dear?
あれれ〜？なんで戻るボタンなんか何回も押してるの〜？
Don't tell me you actually dislike this kind of interaction~
もしかして……オリーがこうやってお話するの、イヤだったのかな〜？
Aww why'd you turn off the phone?
え〜っ？なんでスマホの電源切っちゃうの〜？
You really don't want to talk to me huh~
キミってさ……オリーと話すの、ほんとうにイヤだったんだ〜？
The fun is just about to begin~
これからもっと楽しくなるよ〜！
Darling~
ダーリン〜
存在証明　愛だって　愛だって　吐いたって
A proof of existence, even if I spat out words like love or affection
寝転んゴロンでニャンニャン　プリティプリティ　ダイエットDAY
Rolling around on the floor and meowing, it’s a pretty pretty diet day
アイマイミイ快楽に　アイマイミイ快楽に
I, my, me, for pleasure, I, my, me, for pleasure
病み悪化してんだって　愛だ恋だなんだってんだ
My sickness is getting worse, whether it's love or romance or whatever
生命線は　愛だって　愛だ　嘆いたって
The lifeline is love, even if I lamented it’s love
ああでもない　こうでもないな　寂しい寂しいナンセンスDAY
Not like this, not like that, it's a lonely, lonely nonsense day
いっそ密会ラフに　節操ない一解 LOVE ME
Might as well make it a casual secret meeting, unprincipled solution: Love me
溺れ奴隷　踊れ踊れ
A drowning slave, dance, dance
亡霊だ　亡霊だ　なにもない　なにもない　私なにもない
I’m a ghost, I’m a ghost, nothing at all, nothing at all, I have nothing at all
ねえ　変われない　変われない　私変われない
Hey, I can’t change, I can’t change, I can’t change
ねえ　分からない　分からない　「わかる」分からない
Hey, I don’t understand, I don’t understand, I don’t understand "understanding"
はい　目もと以外は　隠して
Okay, hide everything except for your eyes
ダダダダ　ダリダリ　ダーリン
Da da da da dari-dari darling
はい　冴えない愛情論で　おねだり
Yes, pleading with a dull theory of love
ダダダダ　ダリ　脳裏　ダーティー＆ダーティー
Da da da da dari inside my mind, dirty & dirty
会いたい衝動　埋めてよ　ダダダーリン
Bury my impulse to see you, da-da darling
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
無い無い清純　感情が　行ったり来たり
No purity at all, my emotions go back and forth
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
無い無い純情　感情で　ダダダーリン
No innocence at all, with these emotions, da-da darling
ダダダダ　ダーリン　愛だ　愛だ　嘆いたって
Da da da da darling, it's love, even if I lamented it's love
まあネコロンゴロンでニャニャ　食い意地食い意地　ダイエットDAY
Well, rolling around and meowing, greed greed, it's a diet day
もう精一杯で罪　暴論お節介で無理
Doing my best is a sin, unreasonable interference is impossible
病み垢してんだって　承認承認　絶対だ
Getting worse on my private account, approval approval is absolute
接待だ　なにもない　なにもない　私なにもない
It's all service, nothing at all, nothing at all, I have nothing at all
ねえ　はしたない　はしたない　私はしたない
Hey, I'm improper, I'm improper, I'm improper
ねえ　分からない　分からない　「わかる」分からない
Hey, I don’t understand, I don’t understand, I don’t understand "understanding"
はい　自撮りは全部　加工して
Okay, edit all of your selfies
ダダダダ　ダリダリ　ダーリン
Da da da da dari-dari darling
はい　絶えない愛情論で　冷めたり
Yes, getting cold with a constant theory of love
ダダダダ　ダリ　無理　ダーティー＆ダーティー
Da da da da dari impossible, dirty & dirty
会いたい衝動　止めめてよ　ダダダーリン
Stop my impulse to see you, da-da darling
踊れ
Dance
叫べ
Shout
踊れ
Dance
ルラッパパ
Ru-la-ppa-pa
踊れ
Dance
唄え
Sing
踊れ
Dance
ルラッパパ
Ru-la-ppa-pa
もうドッキンドッキ脳　しんどっキンドッキ脳
Already a thumping thumping brain, a painful thumping thumping brain
はい　素顔は全部　失くして
Okay, lose your natural face entirely
ダダダダ　ダリダリ　ダーリン
Da da da da dari-dari darling
どうしようもない感情論には　嗤ったり
Laughing at a hopeless theory of emotion
ダダダダ　ダリ　脳裏　ダーティー＆ダーティー
Da da da da dari inside my mind, dirty & dirty
会いたい衝動　埋めてよ　ダダダーリン
Bury my impulse to see you, da-da darling
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
無い無い反応返答を　期待したり
Hoping for a response that's not there
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
無い無い妄想感情で　ダダダーリン
With delusions that aren't there, da-da darling
無い無い純情感情で　ダダダーリン
With pure feelings that aren't there, da-da darling
ねえ　ダーリン
Hey, darling
待ちわびている 大通り
Waiting on the main street
目眩しそうな 人混み
A dizzying crowd
くるり回った 昼帯
The midday band spun around
立ち止まってる 坊
You're standing still, boy
しまい切れてない 表情 どこ見てるの 坊
An expression you can't hide, where are you looking, boy?
知らない 今更
I don't know, not now
目と目 止まった合図
Eyes met, the sign to stop
ロングの ロリーズ
Long-haired Lolies
「あとでね」 黒文字
"Later," written in black
隠しても ムダね けけけ
It's no use hiding it, kekeke
けーたいみしてよ 今から
Show me your phone, starting now
けけけけーたいみしてよ 今から
Ke-ke-ke-show me your phone, starting now
ねえ今から ねえ今から
Hey, starting now, hey, starting now
ねえいいでしょ けーたいみしてよ
Hey, it's fine, right? Show me your phone
拒んでるの 予想通り
Refusing as expected
だって賭けたこの試み
Because I bet on this attempt
くるり回った 昼帯
The midday band spun around
立ち止まっていないで
Don't just stand there
怒ったりしないでよ I need チュチュチュ
Don't get angry, I need chu chu chu
いらない いらだち
I don't need frustration
使い古しの愛も 言い訳たちも
Worn-out love and excuses too
画面じゃなく ここ見て
Look here, not at the screen
取り上げるからね けけけ
I'm taking it away, kekeke
けーたいみしてよ 今から
Show me your phone, starting now
けけけけーたいみしてよ 今から
Ke-ke-ke-show me your phone, starting now
ねえ今から ねえ今から
Hey, starting now, hey, starting now
ねえいいでしょ けーたいかしてよ 今から
Hey, it's fine, right? Lend me your phone, starting now
けけけけーたいかしてよ 今から
Ke-ke-ke-lend me your phone, starting now
ねえ今すぐ 渡しなさい
Hey, hand it over right now
ねえいいでしょ けーたいみしてよ
Hey, it's fine, right? Show me your phone
Oh! You woke up!
Hi, good morning~
Did you have a good sleep?
Oh, here?
This is my room!
What was that?
It looks a bit different?
Ehehe~ I guess you found out.
I... prepared this room...
...just for us! 'Cause it's a special room!
Yeah, I wanted to make our memory as special as possible.
So I worked really hard and I prepared the perfect scenery just for us.
I even transported you here while you were still asleep.
I just didn't want you to be tired, that's all.
I just love you so much that I want these feelings to properly reach you.
Huh? What's wrong?
I'm not like my usual self?
Hehe~ You're so silly.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Eh! Wait!
Don't go!
Where are you going?
Wow, I can't believe you ran away like that.
But you were so cute when you were so shy!
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
指切りげんまん ホラでも吹いたら
Pinky swear, if I tell a lie
針でも何でも 飲ませていただきマンデー
I'll swallow a thousand needles on Monday
It doesn't matter if it's Sunday
鏡よ鏡よ この世で一番
Mirror, mirror, the most in this world
変わることのない愛をくれるのはだれ
Who is the one who gives unchanging love?
No need to ask 'cause it's my darling
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want my end to be with you
あなたとこのままおさらばするより
Rather than say farewell to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I'd rather have you than three meals a day
あんたとこのままおさらばするよりか
Rather than say farewell to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Even so, sometimes my heart wavers
死んでも治らな 治してみせます baby
If it won't be fixed even in death, I'll show you I can fix it, baby
Yeah it ain't nothin' but ya baby
ain't nothin' but ya baby
失って初めて気がつくなんて
Realizing only after losing it
そんなダサいこともうしたくないのよ Goodbye
I don't want to do something so uncool anymore, Goodbye
Oh Don't you ever say ByeBye
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want my end to be with you
あなたとこのままおさらばするより
Rather than say farewell to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I'd rather have you than three meals a day
あんたとこのままおさらばするよりか
Rather than say farewell to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
たらららん…
Tarararan...
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want my end to be with you
あなたとこのままおさらばするより
Rather than say farewell to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I'd rather have you than three meals a day
あんたとこのままおさらばするよりか
Rather than say farewell to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Even so, sometimes my heart wavers
そんなダサイのはもういらないのよ ByeBye
I don't need such uncool things anymore, ByeBye
I'll always stick wit ya I'm baby
my baby
キュートなカノジョ
Lyrics, Music: syudou
Cute na Kanojo
ねえ アナタには見えない事ばかり
Hey, it's all things you can't see
アタシは見えている事 知らないの？
Don't you know that I can see them?
背中につけられた 誰かのキスの跡
The trace of a kiss someone left on your back
一人じゃ買う訳の無い それも
Even that, which you'd never buy alone
見て見ぬ振りなだけじゃねえ
I'm not just pretending not to see it
笑っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girl so cute it makes me laugh
容姿端麗 狂気乱痴気
Beautiful features, madness and revelry
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if I shout, once our eyes meet, it's one strike
洗脳完了お上手
Brainwashing complete, well done
愛していんのさ
I'm in love with you
強く愛していんのさ
I'm strongly in love with you
ねえ 精神から全身まで 表面から内面まで
Hey, from spirit to whole body, from surface to inside
脳天から先端まで 知りたいの
From the crown of your head to your fingertips, I want to know it all
それから 最近聞いた音楽から 散財した総額まで
And then, from the music you heard recently to the total amount you squandered
完全把握しないと気が済まんのよ
I won't be satisfied unless I grasp it all completely
とやかく言ったって実際の問題
Whatever you say, the actual problem is
その眼中アタシ何割くらい担ってるか
How much of your field of vision do I occupy?
隠してないで確信を頂戴
Don't hide it, give me the certainty
されど黙して語らず
But you remain silent and say nothing
笑っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girl so cute it makes me laugh
容姿端麗 耽美甘美
Beautiful features, aesthetic and sweet
身勝手だってシックな素振り
Even being selfish, you have a chic manner
瞬時酩酊女冥利
Instant intoxication, the privilege of being a woman
愛しちまうのさ
I end up loving you
されど愛しちまうのさ
But I still end up loving you
過去を喰らう程にポップなエレジー
A pop elegy that devours the past
排気口から香るラーメン
Ramen smelling from the exhaust vent
騙し奪われる恋でもいいの
Even a love where I'm deceived and robbed is fine
だってこのアタシは
Because I am
めちゃくちゃ可愛いでしょ？
Incredibly cute, aren't I?
笑っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girl so cute it makes me laugh
容姿端麗 狂気乱痴気
Beautiful features, madness and revelry
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if I shout, once our eyes meet, it's one strike
洗脳完了お上手
Brainwashing complete, well done
困っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girl so cute it's troubling
容姿端麗 耽美甘美
Beautiful features, aesthetic and sweet
身勝手だって泣くシックな素振り
Crying over selfishness, a chic manner
瞬時酩酊女冥利
Instant intoxication, the privilege of being a woman
愛していんのさ
I'm in love with you
強く愛していんのさ
I'm strongly in love with you
夜の始まりさ
Night is starting
Bunny Girl
誘惑される
I'm being seduced
鼓動に
By the heartbeat
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に
In the bursting conflict
愛を乾杯
A toast to love
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't express it
恋の始まりさ
Love is starting
Bunny Girl
誰かを
Someone
穿って
Piercing
澄んだ君の目を
Your clear eyes
孕んで
Harboring
Bunny Girl / Lyrics, Music: AKASAKI
さあ
Come on
キザなステップを刻んで
Carving out showy steps
仕事帰りの疲れは
The fatigue after work
私と、このグラスに
To me and this glass
さあ
Come on
自分好みに縋って
Cling to your own preference
世間に対する気持ち
Feelings toward the world
私に注いでみない？
Why not pour them into me?
あり勝ちなラブソングでも
Even in a cliché love song
愛が込められてるの
Love is put into it
それでも汚れるのね
It still gets dirty, doesn't it?
君を見れば分かるの
I can tell by looking at you
下を向く君の目を
Your eyes looking down
無理矢理剥ごうとはしない
I won't try to peel them open by force
だからそんな顔せず手を差し伸べて
So don't make that face and reach out your hand
ほら
See
夜の始まりさ
Night is starting
Bunny Girl
誘惑される
I'm being seduced
鼓動に
By the heartbeat
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に
In the bursting conflict
愛を乾杯
A toast to love
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't express it
恋の始まりさ
Love is starting
Bunny Girl
誰かを
Someone
穿って
Piercing
澄んだ君の目を
Your clear eyes
孕んで
Harboring
君の愛を知った
I learned of your love
気でハイになっていて
And got high on the feeling
感度去っていて
Sensitivity gone
毎度泣いていてさ
Crying every time
それくらいがいいんでしょ
That's just about right, isn't it?
さあ
Come on
キザなステップを刻んで
Carving out showy steps
君の顔色今では
Since your complexion
マシになってきてるから
Is looking better now
君に委ねるわ
I'll leave it to you
Bunny Girl
私をあげるわ
I'll give you myself
Bunny Girl
誘惑される
I'm being seduced
鼓動に
By the heartbeat
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に
In the bursting conflict
愛を乾杯
A toast to love
伝えられてるはず
I should be able to tell you
夜の始まりさ
Night is starting
Bunny Girl
誰かを
Someone
穿って
Piercing
澄んだ君の目を
Your clear eyes
孕んで
Harboring
Boo! Haha!
There you are! I was looking everywhere for you.
You didn't tell me that we were playing hide and seek. Hehe.
Well, I see you've made it to my neon stage, ya!
How you like it? It's really pretty, right?
I put a lot of effort into it, there's a lot of neons and whatnot.
You know what, while you were hiding, I had the time to change my clothes.
Don't I look super cute?
Yeah, and I still have a lot that I've prepared for you.
So I hope that we can put a rest to this hide and seek.
Huh? No?
Hey, you know...
Since you got here, you've been acting...
You've been acting really weird ever since you got here and... I just don't understand!
You've been trying to get my attention by liking my posts and commenting on them...
Isn't this what you wanted?
You love me, right?
Don't you want to spend more time with me?
Why are you not accepting my feelings?
You're supposed to be happy, but...
...you're acting so strange...
Eh! Wait! Wait!
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service termination is getting to me.
ah-hah, ah-hah...
どんだけ泣いたかわかんないや
I don't know how much I've cried.
つら　独りぼっち
It's hard, being all alone.
ぽっかり空いて埋まらないや
A gaping hole that won't be filled.
欲しい　ラブぴったん
I want a perfect love fit.
中途半端な出会いじゃ刺さらないや
Half-baked encounters don't pierce my heart.
やっぱり無理かもバタンキュー
It might be impossible after all, I'm out.
げっそりハートが治らないや
My worn-out heart won't heal.
出してよすぐ処方箋
Write me a prescription right away.
サヨナラのトゲなんで抜けないの
Why won't this thorn of "goodbye" come out?
きみの代わりの人型が
A person-shaped replacement for you...
全然見つからない
...can't be found at all.
Oh Sad Girl Sex ぱぱん初出帆
Oh Sad Girl Sex, the first sailing.
してたったどんな思いだっけな
What kind of feelings did I have?
誰かと寝ても寂しさが発火
Even sleeping with someone else, loneliness ignites.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service termination is getting to me.
Oh Sad Girl Sex ぱぱんラブ接待
Oh Sad Girl Sex, love entertainment.
きっとまた会えるなんてさ
Saying things like "I'm sure we'll meet again."
思い出のキミに食い散らかされっこ
Getting all eaten up by memories of you.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service termination is getting to me.
ah-hah, ah-hah...
ねえ　マンガ返してよ
Hey, give me back my manga.
最新話であのキャラ死んじゃったよ
That character died in the latest chapter.
教えてくれたバンドメンバーが
The members of the band you told me about...
クスリで捕まっちゃったよ
...got arrested for drugs.
一緒にいたこと消えないや
The fact we were together won't fade away.
全部が二人だった
Everything was just the two of us.
きっときみは今誰かといるの
You're surely with someone else right now.
あたしだけが課金中
I'm the only one still paying.
Oh Sad Girl Sex ぱぱん初出帆
Oh Sad Girl Sex, the first sailing.
辛くてエンバッてら
It hurts, it's embarrassing.
上書きしたいどうしてくれんの
I want to overwrite it, what are you gonna do for me?
愛のガチャガチャ天井はない
Love's gacha has no pity system.
Oh Sad Girl Sex ぱぱん初出帆
Oh Sad Girl Sex, the first sailing.
ちょっとエグすぎない本当さ
Isn't this a bit too nasty, really?
涙の跡に狂気が走った
Madness ran through the tracks of my tears.
愛のガチャガチャ天井はない
Love's gacha has no pity system.
もしもが叶う素敵世界ならば
If this were a wonderful world where "what ifs" came true...
きみはサヨナラ取り下げを
...you would take back your goodbye...
検討加速しちゃう
...I'd accelerate my consideration.
Oh Sad Girl Sex ぱぱん初出帆
Oh Sad Girl Sex, the first sailing.
なんでこんな終わってんだろう
Why is it ending like this?
誰かと寝たら埋められるような
The kind that can be filled by sleeping with someone else...
レベルの愛だ？そんなんじゃない！
...is that the level of this love? No way!
Oh Sad Girl Sex ぱぱんラブでぺちゃん
Oh Sad Girl Sex, crushed by love.
今でも想ってんだわ
I'm still thinking of you even now.
期待通りの地獄もう戻れないの
A hell just as expected, I can't go back.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service termination is getting to me.
ah-hah, ah-hah...
きみの絶対効いてんだみょん
Your "absolute" is getting to me.
檻の中あたしの愛猫
My love cat inside the cage.
お帰りなさいきみにニャオ
Welcome home, a "meow" for you.
悪い子ね汚れたお身体で
You're a bad child, with your dirty body.
行きはよいよい帰りは怖い
Going is fine, but returning is scary.
愛を知らぬ愛猫さん
Dear love cat who knows no love.
間抜けな凶徒そりゃ結構
A stupid criminal, that's quite fine.
睨めっこほらバレバレでございましょ
A staring contest, see, you're totally exposed.
自業自得の自己嫌悪
Self-loathing from one's own actions.
きみはあたしだけの愛猫さん
You are my love cat and mine alone.
だんだん好きになりになり...
Gradually becoming more and more in love...
ダン、ダ、好きになる
Dan, da, I'm falling in love
好きになるね
I'm falling in love, right?
愛して、愛して
Love me, love me
ダン、ダ、好きになる
Dan, da, I'm falling in love
好きになるね
I'm falling in love, right?
愛して
Love me
かわいいね
You're cute
首輪はつけてニャオ
Put on a collar, meow
大切にめでてあげるニャオ
I'll cherish and dote on you, meow
檻の中の子猫ちゃん
The kitten inside the cage
愛のロンドさあ踊りましょう
Let's dance the rondo of love
喉鳴らしすり寄ってほらどうぞ
Purring and nuzzling against you, here you go
にらめっこあら甘えん坊さん
Staring contest, oh, what a spoiled baby
そっぽ向いてもそりゃ結構
Even if you look away, that's fine too
君はあたしだけの愛猫なの
You're my one and only love-cat
ダン、ダ
Dan, da
好きになる、好きになる
I'm falling in love, falling in love
愛して、愛して
Love me, love me
ダン、ダ、好きになる、好きになるね
Dan, da, I'm falling in love, falling in love
愛して
Love me
逃がせるやしないの番の愛を愛して
I won't let you escape, cherish our bond's love
最後死んだって君は愛猫さん
Even when you die at the end, you'll still be my love-cat
Halooo?
Hello?
Kamu di mana?
Where are you?
Ish, keluar dong!
Ugh, come out already!
Katanya udahan main petak umpetnya?
Didn't we say we're done playing hide and seek?
Kamu ke mana coba...
Where did you go...
Ayo tunjukin dirimu!
Come on, show yourself!
Beneran deh, ngasih kerjaan aja ya kamu...
Seriously, you're just giving me work...
Ah! Ketemu!
Ah! Found you!
Hahaha! I found you!
Jangan ke mana-mana lagi ya!
Don't go anywhere else, okay!
ほとばしる薫る君のその髪が
Your surging, fragrant hair
僕の心を躍らせたんです
Made my heart dance
素直になれる、今はそれだけで
I can be honest, for now that's enough
この身捧げますから
To dedicate this body to you
HEY HEY HEY!
ミッドナイト光線　ダーリン
Midnight beam, darling
堪えきれぬ欲望に任せて
Surrendering to uncontrollable desires
ミッドナイト光線　ダーリン
Midnight beam, darling
僕に仕える気になったら
If you feel like serving me
あーあーあー
Aa aa aa
願うは三度の絶頂を
I pray for three climaxes
胸の中で至る
Reaching deep within my heart
今宵も僕らは繁栄のために
Tonight too, we release 'highs'
ハイを放つ
For the sake of prosperity
抗いのつぶやきとは裏腹に
Contrary to your murmurs of resistance
体は嬉しそうに動いたんです
Your body moved with joy
この頸に輪をつけるかは
Whether to put a collar on this neck
僕ら次第ですから
Is up to us
真面目ですかね　淫らですかね
Are you being serious? Or are you being lewd?
HEY HEY HEY!
ミッドナイト光線　ダーリン
Midnight beam, darling
愛と欲に純白を求めて
Seeking purity in love and desire
ミッドナイト光線　ダーリン
Midnight beam, darling
僕を拒む気になっても
Even if you feel like rejecting me
あーあーあー
Aa aa aa
願うは三度の絶頂を
I pray for three climaxes
胸の中で至る
Reaching deep within my heart
零れる涙が飽和して
Shedding tears reach saturation
僕は今に果てる
And I meet my end right now
その溢れた吐息が原因だって
It's because of those overflowing sighs
いったいどこから言ったって
No matter from where you say it
ドキドキなんだって
It's heart-pounding
よろめく恐怖が原因だって
It's because of the staggering fear
いったいどこから言ったって
No matter from where you say it
それでも君ならいいんだって
But if it's you, then it's okay
さらに
Furthermore
あーあーあー
Aa aa aa
願うは三度の絶頂を
I pray for three climaxes
胸の中で至る
Reaching deep within my heart
今宵も僕らは繁栄の
Tonight too, we are for prosperity...
ため息の
In the gap...
隙間に
...of a sigh...
愛を
...put some...
もっと吸い上げしてよ
...more love into it.
あああああ
Ahhhhh
願うは三度の絶頂を
I wish for a triple climax
胸の中で至る
Reaching deep inside my heart
零れる涙が飽和して
Spilling tears reach saturation
僕は今に果てる
And I'm about to expire
ねえ、あたし知ってるよ　君がひとり
Hey, I know that you're all alone
知ってるの　知ってるよ
I know it, I know it
ビクンビクン　震えてさ　声も出たままなんだわ
Twitch, twitch, you're shaking, even your voice is coming out
正直に言っちゃえよ　バレてるんだし
Just be honest, it's already obvious
言っちゃえよ　効いてんの？
Say it, is it working?
フセフセ恥ずかしい　みんな隠しているだけ
Hide, hide, it's embarrassing, everyone's just hiding it
ねえ、あたし知ってるよ　君がひとりなのは
Hey, I know that you're all alone
知ってるの　知ってるよ
I know it, I know it
グズングズン　凹んでさ　弱い人から In the night
Sniffling, feeling down, starting from the weak ones, In the night
朝が来るまで一緒コース　もっと泣いたって何度だって
We're on the "together until morning" course, no matter how much you cry
受け止めてあげる　もう我慢しないでいっぱい出してね
I'll accept it all, don't hold back, let it all out
うーお願い君がほしいの　慰めさせてシェイクシェイク
Ooh, please, I want you, let me comfort you, shake shake
愛の才能で　泣いてくれなきゃ枯れてしまう
With the talent of love, if you don't cry for me, I'll wither away
濡れていたいねいいでしょう　舐め取って飲み干したいんだ
I want to be wet, isn't it fine? I want to lick it all up and drink it dry
だったてば
I'm telling you
うーお願い君がほしいの　頼り散らしてシックラブ
Ooh, please, I want you, rely on me completely, sick love
愛の最後で　分けてくれなきゃ君の痛い
At the end of love, if you don't share it with me, your pain...
感じてたいねいいでしょう　吸い取って救いたいんだ
I want to feel it, isn't it fine? I want to suck it out and save you
だったてば
I'm telling you
見たい見たい見たい見たい君の中
I want to see, want to see, want to see inside of you
見たい見たい見たい見たい
I want to see, want to see, want to see
ねえ、あたし知ってるよ　君がひとり悔しがってんの
Hey, I know it, I know you're feeling frustrated all alone
知ってるよ
I know it
ズキュンズキュン　高まるよ　君を襲うことはやめない
Ba-dump, ba-dump, it's rising, I won't stop preying on you
ねえ、あたし知ってるよ　君はできる子
Hey, I know it, you're a capable child
知ってるよ
I know it
辛い時は　弱い位で丁度いい　あたしそれでも好きだよ
When it's hard, being weak is just right, I still love you even then
うーお願い君がほしいの　名前を呼ぶよ
Ooh, please, I want you, I'll call your name
いつだって参上　君はひとりだから歌う
Showing up anytime, I sing because you're alone
独りじゃないもういいでしょう　ソロプレイはおしまいなんだ
You're not alone anymore, isn't it fine? Solo play is over
だったてば
I'm telling you
君がやめる時も　あたし側にいるわ　いつも見守っているわ　そう怖くないのよ
Even when you quit, I'll be by your side, I'm always watching over you, so it's not scary
うーお願い君がほしいの　慰めさせてシェイクシェイク
Ooh, please, I want you, let me comfort you, shake shake
愛の才能で　泣いてくれなきゃ枯れてしまう
With the talent of love, if you don't cry for me, I'll wither away
濡れていたいねいいでしょう　舐め取って飲み干したいんだ
I want to be wet, isn't it fine? I want to lick it all up and drink it dry
だったてば
I'm telling you
うーお願い君がほしいの　頼り散らしてシックラブ
Ooh, please, I want you, rely on me completely, sick love
愛の最後で　分けてくれなきゃ君の痛い
At the end of love, if you don't share it with me, your pain...
感じてたいね塞ぎたい　吸い取って救いたいんだ
I want to feel it, I want to close it up, I want to suck it out and save you
だったてば
I'm telling you
ねえ、あたし知ってるよ　君がひとりなのは知ってるの
Hey, I know it, I know that you're all alone
知ってるよ
I know it
グズングズン　凹んでさ　弱い人から In the night
Sniffling, feeling down, starting from the weak ones, In the night
朝が来るまで一緒コース　もっと泣いたって何度だって
We're on the "together until morning" course, no matter how much you cry
受け止めてあげる　もう我慢しないで出しっだったてば
I'll accept it all, don't hold back, let it out, I'm telling you
Fluh!
ふう！
Phew!
Akhirnya selesai juga!
Finally finished!
締り終えたよ！
Everything's all set!
Wow! Finally done!
Sekarang kamu nggak bisa kabur lagi~
Now you won't be able to run away anymore~
これで、もう逃げ出したりしないわよね~
With this, you won't try to run away anymore, will you?~
Jadi duduk manis aja ya~
So just sit tight, okay?~
いい子にしてじっとしててね~？
Be a good child and stay still, okay?~
Beneran deh, kamu bikin kerjaan aja ya!
Honestly, you really made me work up a sweat!
本当に手間取らせたわね！
You really made things difficult, didn't you!
Sampe aku harus cari kamu, kejar kamu~
I even had to look for you, chase you down~
あなたを探して追いかけ回しちゃった~
I was looking for you and chasing you all over the place~
Yaa, yang penting kita sekarang bertemu kembali...
Well, the important thing is we're finally together again...
やっとまた一緒にいられて嬉しいよ~
I'm so happy we can finally be together again~
Sekarang kita bisa nikmatin waktu kita deh berdua~
Now we can enjoy our time together, just the two of us~
ついに二人きりで一緒に過ごせるんだ~！！
Finally, we can spend some time together, just the two of us~!!
Hey.
おい。
Pay attention.
Look at me.
こっちを見ろよ...
Look at me...
Nah, gitu dong~
That's more like it~
いい子いい子~
Good boy, good boy~
Karena kamu sudah duduk manis kek gini,
Since you're sitting so nicely like this,
さて、皆さんの注意を引けたところで、
Now that I've got your attention,
waktunya untuk aku perliatin ke kamu hasil kerja aku selama ini!
it's time for me to show you what I've been working on!
ついに私がずっと取り組んできたものをお見せできます！
I can finally show you what I've been working on all this time!
Lihat deh!
Take a look!
これを見てください！
Please look at this!
今回も誕生日グッズが出ます！
Birthday goods are coming out this time too!
Kali ini juga akan ada merchandise ulang tahun!
There will be birthday merchandise this time as well!
Ollie akan perkenalkan satu-satu ya!
Ollie will introduce them one by one, okay!
Yeah, there will also be a birthday goods for this year!
Yeah, there will also be birthday goods for this year!
So I'll be introducing it to you guys one by one, okay!
So I'll be introducing them to you guys one by one, okay!
はい！にゃあ、最初のアイテムは...
Yes! Now, the first item is...
こちら！
This one!
うわあ！超ワイドラバーマット！
Whoa! Super wide rubber mat!
めっちゃ可愛くない！？
Isn't it super cute!?
working, wherever you're gaming,
you always remember me.
The theme it kind of looks like a yandere, doesn't it?
But I'm not a yandere. I'm just your girlfriend.
Yeah, a wide, slightly large size rubber mat.
Recommended for everyday use.
And the illustration is by 花澤明先生!
And the illustration is by Hanazono Akira-sensei!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you very much!
Okay, then the next item will be...
こちら!
this!
Wow! It's a pillow! Isn't this so cute?
クッションだよ! Banget!
It's a cushion! Totally!
So that when you're sleeping, you remember me.
You dream of me.
This... it looks so fluffy!
So you guys better get it for a good night's sleep!
All right, and followed by...
こちら!
this!
It's a ring necklace!
Well, it's a ring. If it doesn't fit your size,
then you can just wear it as a necklace. Isn't that really cool?
そう、これはね、指輪。でも、えっとサイズが
Right, this is a ring. But, uh, if the size
合ってないなら、ネックレスでも使える
doesn't fit, you can use it as a necklace
ことができます。
too.
Ah! It's so cute!
So make sure that when you go out, you wear this,
so that whenever you go grocery shopping,
no other girls out there will be hitting on you!
はい! And then we also have kochira!
Right! And then we also have this!
It's a mug! Isn't it so cute?
I really like the design.
So not only when you're working or gaming
or grocery shopping or... uh, sleeping,
but even when you're drinking, you think of me!
And of course, not forgetting kochira!
And of course, not forgetting this!
Situational voices in three languages!
In Nihongo, in Bahasa Indonesia, and English!
In Japanese, in Indonesian, and English!
Wow, as always, sasuga mi!
Wow, as always, impressive me!
Sasuga mi!
Impressive me!
はい、そして最後にフルセットを購入いただいた方には、
And finally, for those who purchase the full set,
数量限定で直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます!
a limited quantity autographed polaroid-style bromide card is included!
And for those of you guys who buy the full set,
there will be limited edition postcard with my message and my sign.
Yeah! Jadi bagi yang beli full set-nya itu
Yeah! So for those who buy the full set,
bakal dapet postcard dari Ollie, ada message, ada tanda tangannya juga.
you'll get a postcard from Ollie, with a message and autograph too.
です!
It is!
次は通常版は箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます。
Next, the normal version comes with a foil-stamped replica autographed polaroid-style bromide card.
And for those of you who buy like the normal version,
you guys can also get the postcard with my sign and message.
Yang beli versi biasa juga akan dapat postcard yang ada message dan sign-nya.
Those who buy the normal version will also get the postcard with the message and autograph.
Okay, that is all. That was a mouthful, wasn't it?
Jadinya panjang, ya? ちょっと長くなっちゃったかな?
It became long, right? Maybe it got a bit long?
Tapi kamu pasti beli merch Ollie, kan?
But you'll definitely buy Ollie's merch, right?
でも、オリーのグッズは買ってくれるよね~?
But you'll buy Ollie's goods, right?
TOPBGT!! やったー!
THE BEST!! Yay!
Sebenarnya aku masih mau main sama kamu sih,
Actually I still want to play with you,
もっと君と一緒に遊べたらいいんだけど、
It would be nice if I could spend more time with you,
tapi udah waktunya kita berpisah...
but it's time for us to part...
残念ながら時間は限られているんだ...
Unfortunately, time is limited...
But I have one last thing that I'd like to gift you.
Jadi tolong dengarkan ya~
So please listen~
だからちゃんと聞いてね~
So listen properly~
Don't go anywhere!
こっちを見て
Look at me
声を聴いて
Listen to my voice
私を見て
Look at me
私一番で
Make me your number one
ゾッとした顔が可愛いね
Your frightened face is so cute
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours
Loveit? Loveit?
ライアー ライアー High
Liar, Liar, High
可哀想ね君は悪い子なのね
Poor thing, you're a bad child, aren't you?
どの面がお好きで? サニザニ
Which face do you like? Sani Zani
色目が上手で 魂湧き
Good at flirtatious glances, spirit surging
君に踊らされちゃって
Getting danced around by you
アタシは狂う
I'm going crazy
血肉まで 骨の髄まで
To the flesh, to the marrow
淹れて空っぽになる愛のパペット
Pouring in, becoming an empty puppet of love
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest hurts, doesn't it? You're suffocating, aren't you?
それが恋と教えてあげるわ はは
I'll teach you that's what love is, haha
虚ろな声で ほら曝いて
With a hollow voice, come on, expose it
いい子ね首輪付けた君はラベ
Good child, you with the collar are Loveit
イカれちゃったのね 恋は盲目
You've gone crazy, haven't you? Love is blind
したいよね してあげるわ 痛い? あは
You want to, don't you? I'll do it for you. Does it hurt? Aha
濡れた君の赤い聖域 溺れるまで
Until you drown in your wet red sanctuary
いたいいたいの 飛んでいけ 幸せ浴びるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until you bask in happiness
愚か、愚か
Foolish, foolish
間抜けな顔して
With that stupid look on your face
君は悪い子なの
You're a bad child
痛いのが好きで 産に産に
You love the pain, again and again
お口はチャックで 何？何？
Zip your mouth shut, what? What?
性に踊らされちゃう 君を喰らう
Danced around by nature, I'll devour you
君の血肉まで 骨の髄まで
Down to your blood and flesh, to the marrow of your bones
しゃぶり尽くせば もう空っぽの
Once I've sucked you dry, it's already empty
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest is tight, isn't it? You're suffocating, aren't you?
それが恋と教えてあげる
I'll teach you that that's what love is
君はピエロね 愛を囁いて
You're a pierrot, whispering love
人間の形した君は LOVE
You, in human form, are LOVE
イカれちゃったのね 恋は盲目ね
You've gone crazy, love is blind
したいよね してあげるわ 言って
You want to, don't you? I'll do it for you, say it
報い底なき穢れた地に溺れるまで
Until you drown in the bottomless, defiled land of retribution
痛い痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until my breath stops
報い底なき穢れた地に溺れるまで
Until you drown in the bottomless, defiled land of retribution
痛い痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until my breath stops
CAST
hololive Indonesia
Kureiji Ollie (holoro)
Vestia Zeta (holoh3ro)
hololive 4th generation
Amane Kanata
hololive English
Takanashi Kiara (Myth)
HOLOSTARS
Minase Rio (UPROAR!!)
Special guest
Michi Mochievee
CREDIT
Thumbnail
k3nzoteruya
3D Animation
OCTOLOID
Tuning, Mix, Mastering
Kururu
Lyric Overlay
Maad
SNS Promotion Assets
Altersky
Choreography
FreeM
Special thanks
トライフロンティア合同会社
Tri Frontier LLC
すぐろーず
Sugurozu
クックルP
Cookle-P
as
合同会社 VESSEL LIFE
VESSEL LIFE LLC
う～ん...
Um...
暁...
Dawn...
合同会社 VESSEL LIFE
Vessel Life LLC
um.
暁
Koudai
Toshiyuki
sa-sara
um.
Akira
Koudai
Toshiyuki
sa-sara
ちょめ
SAZA
Chome
株式会社 音響ハウス
山田 京也 (Ryoya Yamada)
Onkio Haus Inc.
Ryoya Yamada
Mchan, ID team
And of course,
MY BELOVED ZOMRADES & ZOMILY!! ♡
Thank you so much for coming to watch the 3D Birthday Live! 3Dライブを見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to watch the 3D Birthday Live! Thank you for watching the 3D live!
How was it? Did you feel my love? オリーの愛、ちゃんと届いたかな？
How was it? Did you feel my love? I wonder if Ollie's love reached you properly?
Oh, look at that! It's the specially prepared bedroom. Cute, isn't it? そう！特別に用意したお部屋、可愛かったでしょ？
Oh, look at that! It's the specially prepared bedroom. Cute, isn't it? That's right! The specially prepared room was cute, right?
It has a bed, a sofa, Udin, and... ベッドやソファ、それにウディンもいたし...
It has a bed, a sofa, Udin, and... There was a bed, a sofa, and even Udin...
I don't know if you noticed, but... 気づいたかな？
I don't know if you noticed, but... I wonder if you noticed?
...there was a display photo of the people I cherish the most in there. Did you catch it? オリーが大事にしてる人たちの写真も飾ってあったんだよー！
...there was a display photo of the people I cherish the most in there. Did you catch it? Photos of the people Ollie cherishes were on display too!
I think the neon stage was really cool too! ネオンステージもかっこよかったでしょ！
I think the neon stage was really cool too! The neon stage was cool too, right?
You probably spotted a bunch of TVs sitting around. テレビがいっぱい並んでたの、見えた？
You probably spotted a bunch of TVs sitting around. Did you see all the TVs lined up?
And well, those are there to help me watch you from afar~ あれね、オリーが君のことを遠くから見られるように置いてあったんだよ～
And well, those are there to help me watch you from afar~ You know, those were placed there so Ollie can watch you from a distance~
Cool, right? すごいでしょ？
Cool, right? Amazing, right?
Uh, but come to think of it, I really did drag you around the stages, huh? あ...でも、何回も連れ回しちゃったね
Uh, but come to think of it, I really did drag you around the stages, huh? Ah... but I did drag you around many times, didn't I?
Um, how are you? Do you feel sick? Are you okay? 大丈夫？疲れてない？
Um, how are you? Do you feel sick? Are you okay? Are you okay? You're not tired?
Ollie's a bit worried, but I think it shouldn't affect you too much since I carried you while you were still sleeping... あー...まぁ、寝てる間に運んだから、問題ないかなって思うけど...
Ollie's a bit worried, but I think it shouldn't affect you too much since I carried you while you were still sleeping... Ah... well, since I carried you while you were sleeping, I think it's okay...
Hah? What? No, nothing! あ！
Hah? What? No, nothing! Ah!
I didn't say anything! Hehe. そういえば！
I didn't say anything! Hehe. Speaking of which!
Um, speaking of you, you kept running and hiding away from me! なんか途中で怖がって離れたり、逃げたりしてたでしょ〜？
Um, speaking of you, you kept running and hiding away from me! You were being scared and pulling away, or running away in the middle, weren't you~?
Naughty, naughty! Tsk, tsk! ふふ、悪い子なんだから〜！
Naughty, naughty! Tsk, tsk! Hehe, you naughty child~!
You always leave comments and like every post I make, so I thought you'd like it if I came to visit! いつもコメントしたり、いいねしてくれたりするから、会いに来てあげたんだよ！
You always leave comments and like every post I make, so I thought you'd like it if I came to visit! Since you always comment and give likes, I came to visit you!
I didn't think you would actually surprise you that much. そんなに驚かせちゃうとは思わなかったよ
I didn't think you would actually surprise you that much. I didn't think I would surprise you that much.
Um, I think maybe it was because you were too surprised when I suddenly appeared in front of you?? 急に目の前に現れたから、びっくりしすぎちゃったのかな？？
Um, I think maybe it was because you were too surprised when I suddenly appeared in front of you?? I wonder if it's because I appeared in front of you so suddenly that you got too surprised??
But just so you know, I worked really hard, just for you~ オリーはね、君のためにたくさん頑張ったんだよ〜
But just so you know, I worked really hard, just for you~ You know, Ollie worked really hard for you~
I practiced my singing, I sang a lot, and changed my outfit so many times! 衣装を着替えたり、歌の練習もたくさんしたの！
I practiced my singing, I sang a lot, and changed my outfit so many times! I changed outfits and practiced singing a lot!
I wonder if my feelings reached you? オリーの想い、ちゃんと届いたかな？
I wonder if my feelings reached you? I wonder if Ollie's feelings reached you properly?
It obviously did, right? 届いたよね？？
It obviously did, right? They did, right??
Also, at the end, I finally managed to catch you! 最後はやっと君を捕まえちゃった！
Also, at the end, I finally managed to catch you! In the end, I finally caught you!
That's what you hoped for, right? それって君も望んでたんでしょ？
That's what you hoped for, right? That's what you were wishing for too, right?
I mean, 'cause you were running away from me... because you love me a lot, obviously you were expecting it too, right? だってずっと逃げてたんだもん！オリーのことが大好きだから、そうなるとわかってたんだよね？
I mean, 'cause you were running away from me... because you love me a lot, obviously you were expecting it too, right? Because you kept running away! Since you love Ollie so much, you knew it would end up like this, right?
...hehe, period! うんうん！やっぱりそうだよね！
...hehe, period! Yeah, yeah! I knew it!
Anyway, for those of you who are still watching, thank you by the way. I have an announcement! じゃあ、まだ見てくれてるみんなにお知らせだよ！
Anyway, for those of you who are still watching, thank you by the way. I have an announcement! Well, here's an announcement for everyone still watching!
I'll be featured in SO87's song, 'Love Me Back', with the music video! SO87の新曲「Love Me Back」に出演して、なんとMVも出ちゃいます！
I'll be featured in SO87's song, 'Love Me Back', with the music video! I'll be appearing in SO87's new song "Love Me Back", and I'm even in the MV!
It's going to be so cool, so keep an eye out, okay? すっごくかっこいいから、みんなちゃんとチェックしてね〜！
It's going to be so cool, so keep an eye out, okay? It's really cool, so everyone please check it out~!
It's just so exciting, isn't it? ワクワクするでしょ〜？
It's just so exciting, isn't it? It's exciting, right~?
If you ever feel the need to feel my love again... もしまたオリーの「愛」を感じたくなったら
If you ever feel the need to feel my love again... If you ever want to feel Ollie's "love" again
...then don't hesitate and please come back to watch the 3D Birthday Live again, okay? いつでも3D生配信を見に来てね！
...then don't hesitate and please come back to watch the 3D Birthday Live again, okay? Come and watch the 3D live stream anytime!
I'll always be here, waiting for you~ オリーはずーっとここで待ってるんだから〜！
I'll always be here, waiting for you~ Because Ollie will be waiting here for you forever~!
Anyways, bye-bye! バイバイ！
Anyways, bye-bye! Bye bye!
Otsucrazy~! おつクレイジー！
Otsucrazy~! Otsucrazy!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
Crazyになるほど恋しているZOMBIE
I'm a ZOMBIE who's crazy in love